Are you serious, Lando?
You brought a typewriter here?
Do you know that this typewriter is magical?
This thing can change your life.
I trusted you, but you're a traitor!
Go ahead, kill me!
I'm not scared to die!
I won't let my dad kill you.
I will take the bullet for you.
We'll be together.
This is what I want.
This is my wish.
I just want to make sure
my loved ones are safe.
Aunt Tess is safe.
- And Joyce, too.
- Dex!
Liam is my husband.
It's not enough that
I bring you back to life, Liam.
I can find a way to remove Joyce
from your life.
Via.
Forgive me, Sabel.
I was blinded.
I was blinded by my love for you.
I don't know if I can call it love.
If only I could turn back time,
I wouldn't even try
to separate the two of you.
Sabel...
Diego...
Forgive me.
Maybe this is my curse.
I'm the only one
who can't use this typewriter.
I'm the only one who can't turn back time
to correct my mistakes.
Hans, I don't blame Liam
for turning himself in.
I wish I knew where he is.
Joyce, I know you love Liam.
But...
while I'm here...
I hope I'll be enough to make you feel safe.
I'm sorry, Hans.
Sorry.
I know why it is Liam.
Not because you're lacking.
But because...
I have loved Liam ever since.
What do you mean, Joyce?
You've been with Liam before we got together?
Hans, I'm sorry.
I need to know where Liam is.
I need your help.
Please.
I'm sorry, Hans.
But I feel like there's something
you're not telling me.
What are you doing?
Miss, it's just me.
You don't need to pretend.
I even changed my outfit so it'd be safe.
I'm just pretending to be a cripple.
But my wound and stitches really hurt.
What are you doing here?
So cranky.
Didn't I tell you to notify me first?
What if Liam sees you?
You're so cranky. Where's Sir Liam?
He went out to buy medicine.
He'll be back anytime soon, Queenie.
Where? In town?
It will take him a while, for sure.
I got you your favorites.
Wine.
Right? I told you.
You just lack faith in me.
With this, here.
See?
Let's have some wine.
Here.
Here's the cash you asked me to withdraw.
See?
So...
don't you have any plans of going home?
I'm only starting to get Liam's trust.
- More.
- Okay.
I missed this.
Via?
Hans?
What are you doing here?
What if someone's following you?
Why?
Are you surprised to see me?
Are you scared that Ramon will find you?
What have you been doing?
After you exposed everything, Liam...
you even got your family involved,
and Joyce, and her family.
You'll just hide here?
Liam, why...
Why did Joyce choose you?
- You're a coward.
- Hans, you don't understand.
I just need to take care of Via first.
Then I'll go back to Joyce.
Take care of Via?
What are you talking about?
What kind of excuse is that, Liam?
I can understand if you and Via
are on the brink of death,
but it looks like...
Look at your situation.
It seems like you're playing house!
Wait until I tell Joyce about
what you've been doing with Via.
I'm done with your excuses, Liam.
You've fooled everyone.
Is that really your reason?
Is that it?
Or do you have an agenda?
You're a jerk.
What? What are you saying?
Oh no!
That's Attorney Hans.
What is he doing here?
Mister, I'm getting off here.
Thank you so much for giving me a ride.
I'm sorry, it took us a whole day
for this trip.
Here's my payment.
It's all yours.
You don't have to give me change.
Thank you so much.
Be safe.
I gave way, but you're telling me I'm wrong!
- You really didn't give way!
- Yet I'm still the bad guy?
The truth is, you're waiting for me to fail!
I can't go downstairs.
Attorney Hans is already
killing your boyfriend, Miss.
Are you still going
to pretend that you can't walk?
Come on, Queenie!
- Make no mistake!
- Attorney!
Sir Liam, that's enough.
Liam, that's enough.
Stop!
Hey! Hey, stop!
Stop, stop, stop!
Via.
You can walk?
Love, I can explain.
- Love...
- Via, you fooled me.
No.
Come on.
Hear me out. Just let me explain first, okay?
Liam.
Joyce?
Joyce.
I want to get mad at you.
I want to get mad about
all the mistakes you made.
In this world and in our past life.
Do you believe me now?
I do, Liam.
I believe you, but I hate you.
I want to ask how you could do that?
Why did you choose to lose your son and me?
Joyce, forgive me.
I was a coward.
I forgot to fight.
Forgive me because...
I became selfish.
I thought you would be happy.
But I was wrong, Joyce.
I regret it so much because I know
that I will pay for this my whole life.
I know in my heart...
that I will forgive you a hundred times over.
Let's go home.
Come on, let's go home.
No! No!
- No!
- Via...
You're not going anywhere, Liam!
You're not leaving.
He's not leaving.
No.
Via, that's enough.
Don't trap yourself in the illusion of love
you're trying to believe in.
Save some for yourself.
You have the guts to say that
because he chose you!
You will never understand me, Joyce!
You don't know how it feels!
You have no idea!
You don't know.
Via, as women,
we should not let our world
revolve around a man.
Via, we don't beg for love.
Love shouldn't be forced.
I hope you understand that
real love knows how to sacrifice...
How to set things free.
If that's the case, then set Liam free!
Via!
That's enough.
Let them be happy.
No...
No!
You're not leaving, Liam.
Liam, please.
Please.
I won't let my dad kill you.
I will take the bullet for you.
This is what I want.
This is my wish.
Did you use the typewriter?
Via...
Via, it always comes with a price.
I don't care, Liam!
I can't bear losing you.
I can't bear it.
- I don't care what the price is.
- Via...
Via!
Via, please stop.
That's enough. Stop.
Liam, please.
- Stop. That's enough...
- Please, please, please.
Via.
Think about it carefully.
Sorry.
Via.
Via, listen to me.
Just this once,
love yourself.
Let go of me!
Let's go.
Liam, Joyce.
I made a promise to your family.
What's that?
Go hide.
Hide. Stay there!
- Don't...
- Edmond!
Stay there!
Edmond, stay here...
Madam, I don't want to die yet.
What's going on?
I'm moving.
Who is it?
Who's there?
- Who are you?
- Oh...
What a lovely night for a reunion.
Ramon dela Peña?
Who are you?
Go inside.
Joyce...
Leave my family alone!
Edmond!
You're a demon!
Demon!
Don't touch me!
Edmond, Edmond...
Why is this happening?
What's going on here?
- Mom!
- Liam, my son!
- Mom, Mom.
- Dad!
You took so long!
Dad...
Stay away from me!
You're so evil!
Where's my daughter?
She's alive.
So I'm begging you, Ramon.
Stop this!
It's not too late!
It's really not too late.
Okay?
You're still alive.
This is your chance to retract...
every lie you said against me!
Okay?
You will admit that you're the mastermind.
You killed Lando, and you shot Via.
You really are crazy, aren't you?
I won't commit any more sins!
Why?
If they all die...
wouldn't it be your fault
because you didn't do as I say?
Don't! Don't! Don't!
Don't...
- Answer me!
- Don't...
Don't...
Oh my God, Miss Via. What happened here?
I still want to become
Escale's editor-in-chief.
Shut up, Queenie.
What happened here?
Who are you?
What will you do with a typewriter?
Get that.
Just get that.
Did you get hit
in the back or in the head?
- Don't!
- Ramon!
Kill me instead.
Go on.
Go on and kill me!
For this to end!
I'm the one who did you wrong! Kill me!
Don't get them involved!
You can't tell me what to do.
Okay?
You've been fooling me, Liam.
Death is not enough
for all the betrayal and hurt
you did to my daughter and me.
How can I be sure they're safe?
That you'll keep them out of this?
You won't know.
You have no choice but to do as I say.
Are you just going to use me
to clean your name?
I will do it.
But don't ever get them involved.
No one will get involved...
if you do what I say.
Just remember how you became
my puppet before.
Hi, baby boy.
You know, for some reason,
my boss needs that typewriter.
I'll just buy it from you.
I don't want to fight, you know.
It's not my brand.
I'm good at lip-sync, but...
Just give it to me
if you don't want to get hurt.
No!
- Give it to me.
- No.
- No!
- Give it to me!
- Stop!
- No!
- Give it to me!
- This is mine!
- Stop!
- Let me have it!
This is mine! Let go...
Give it to me!
Watch over him.
My baby...
Sorry.
Dad!
Stop this!
There's still another way.
Here's the typewriter, Dad!
- Here it is!
- You again?
I got the typewriter!
Dad, this has powers!
This can change everything.
Everything.
Everything in the past can change.
We can be complete again.
You've gone crazy like your mom!
Hans, now!
Dad!
Dad, go on. Run! Call the police. Dad, go on!
Help them escape!
- Dad!
- My God, Danilo!
Stop it!
Joyce, Joyce!
Give it to me!
Joyce!
- Joyce!
- Help Joyce, Mom!
- Try to move, Ramon.
Liam, I'll take care of this!
Dad! Dad!
Joyce!
- Via!
- Joyce!
Via!
Via, that's enough!
Via, stop.
- Stop it. That's enough!
- Joyce...
Stop it.
Liam, move.
Stop.
My dear...
Joyce...
Mom...
What do I change?
What should I do? I don't know.
What do I do? What do I change?
Dear, do what is right.
Do what is right, dear.
I will write...
I will write it that Ramon didn't find us.
That's how I will revise it.
No, dear.
Do it right.
I'm begging you.
Go back to when Liam
first used the typewriter.
Dear, please.
Do it.
I don't want to hurt you, Liam!
But if I need to shoot you, I will.
Can't you see, Liam? I'm doing this for us.
This is for us. I just want...
I just want us to return to how we were...
The way it used to be.
Promise... Promise, I won't hurt you.
- I will just erase Joyce.
- Via...
I will take her out of our lives.
Via, that's not true love!
What about you, Mom?
You will disappear...
Dear, I'm okay.
- Mom...
- I'm okay, Joyce.
I'm okay.
I'm ready.
I'm happy with the time I was given to meet
- and be with you again.
- Mom...
No.
Do it.
Go on. Do what's right.
That's not real love if you
control things with the typewriter.
Even if there's a typewriter,
the heart will always know, Via.
We write our own stories.
And even though we've met...
Joyce is the only one I love.
Leave us be.
Liam.
Sorry.
Look what you did, Joyce!
- Liam, dear.
- Liam!
Liam, dear.
This is your fault!
- Via!
- This is your fault.
Give me the typewriter!
Liam, dear.
Give it to me!
Promise me that you will be
a good husband and father.
I am content with the chance
I had to be with you, son.
- I love you so much.
- Mom, I love you so much.
Miss Via, that's enough!
Miss Via...
Joyce!
Before you use the typewriter,
know that your son will still die.
He won't be able to survive the operation.
Give it to me.
Liam, can't you see?
This is all for you.
Everything is for you, Liam.
True love means facing problems together.
Forgive me, Liam...
If I gave up that time.
I forgot why we chose
to hold each other's hands.
I wish I didn't let anger
get the better of me.
I wish I didn't leave you.
I wish we had faced our problem together,
with Dex.
I love you so much, Joyce.
I love you so much, too, Liam.
I forgive you.
Let's go back to our old life.
Liam...
Joyce, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Liam, forgive me too.
Forgive me, too, for everything I said.
I'm sorry.
I regret that we've come to this point, Liam.
I wanted us to return to the time
before you used the typewriter.
Because I would stop you
from using the typewriter,
and you wouldn't know its power.
I wanted to be your ally.
I wanted to be by your side
while we deal with the challenges.
I love you so much, Liam.
Liam...
Dex is gone.
Our son is gone.
No, Joyce.
Joyce, no.
No, no...
No, no, no.
No!
No, Joyce...
No, Joyce.
Joyce, no!
Joyce...
I chose to come back with you
even though I know the price to pay.
We will fight together, Liam.
Dex, Dex...
No.
[Dexter T. Herrera]
Happy 40th day, my son.
[April 3, 2015 - March 22, 2022]
It's my fault that this happened to our son.
Hon, no.
Joyce...
I want your suffering to end.
What do you mean?
I gave you...
a miserable life.
I brought you this tragedy.
I was also the reason for the hardships
that you went through.
You and my son.
I'm a worthless father.
I'm a worthless husband, Joyce.
Hon, no...
Hon, don't say that.
We'll get through this together.
The two of us.
Liam, forgive me.
Forgive me if I made you feel
you're not enough. That's wrong.
Honestly, I was the one who wasn't content.
I know it in my heart.
Hon, please.
You're right, Joyce.
All this happened because I'm weak...
Because I made mistakes.
You don't deserve a husband like me.
I hope you understand...
that I'm doing this for you.
Believe it or not...
I only want you to be happy.
I can't bear to see you
continue to get hurt because of me.
Maybe I should...
I should stay away from you.
Liam...
Liam.
I'm setting you free.
Using the typewriter
has a price to pay indeed.
I thought we would
get through this together...
That we would hold on together.
But I was wrong.
Maybe this is the end of our story.
Dad...
I can't understand...
why this had to happen to my son.
It hurts.
It hurts so much.
It hurts so much, Dad.
This is all my fault.
This is all my fault, Dad.
Mommy Tess...
Mom, please forgive me.
Sorry I was not able to fight.
Forgive me for wasting your sacrifice...
because we're no longer together.
I promise you, Mom.
I will wait until Liam
can finally forgive himself
for what happened to our son.
I'm sorry, son.
I'm no God to use the typewriter
to bring you back to life.
Rest in peace, Dex, my son.
Your dad and I love you so much.
[Three years later]
Dex, my son...
Mom's already here in Paris.
I have already fulfilled my life-long dream.
Too bad, your dad and I
couldn't fulfill it together.
- Mommy?
- Joyce!
- Dad.
- How's your vacation?
It's good.
Too bad I couldn't bring
the two of you with me.
Don't worry about us, dear.
We're happy if you're happy.
You have finally fulfilled your dream.
You really are in Paris.
Joyce, sorry, I don't want to say this.
I don't want to ruin your vacation, but...
you have to know that...
The annulment papers that Liam filed
already arrived.
What's your plan, my dear?
Are you really going to file an annulment?
Did Liam already show up?
The lawyers are the only ones who answer us.
I won't stop Liam...
if that's what he wants, Mom.
It'll be a waste, dear.
Someone's calling me.
It might be Liam.
Mom, that's impossible.
He won't call me.
I'll hang up now.
Bye, Mom. Bye, Dad.
I love you.
I love you, dear. Enjoy it there, dear.
Miss Malvarosa?
I am now Mrs. Baudin.
The city of love didn't fail me.
I have found my forever in Paris.
I'm so happy for you, Mrs. Malvarosa.
Mrs. Baudin.
I am happy for what you've become, Joyce.
Imagine.
Who would have thought
that my most beautiful student
is also kind-hearted?
I've long been wanting to work
for a children's foundation.
How is it to be Liam's wife?
We separated after what happened to our son.
Your lectures were correct.
There's no permanent thing in this life.
Everything can change.
Like the pain in here.
It can go away eventually...
like the change you longed for yourself
and your loved ones.
Who knows?
Your situation with Liam can still change.
It's not too late.
Wherever life takes me,
whatever change happens, I will accept it.
The beauty of Paris will help you
let go of the burden you feel.
I hope so.
By the way, I have a Filipino friend
who gives tours here in Paris.
It's my treat
for one of my favorite students.
I will include your name in the list
of those who will tour
with his agency today, okay?
Thank you so much, ma'am.
You're welcome.
All our happy memories...
were replaced by painful ones, Liam.
I hope you also slowly
get through all the bitterness.
Liam.
For the last time,
before we bid each other goodbye,
tell me everything you want to say.
Get straight to the point.
When I saw you here,
I was reminded of my mistakes.
Let's make it happy
if this is where we will separate.
[Via dela Peña rocking at the Fashion Week
in the city of love!]
Sorry, bro.